The culture of police is greater than the individual.
I did a post about Chief Davis and how I felt she was absolutely capping when she was talking to Don Lemon.
People were saying, Amanda, she is a black woman.
She's dealing with a lot.
Here, Hannah Drake has so graciously compiled a few reasons why Chief Davis in Memphis is culpable in the tragedy that happened with Tyree Nichols.
Her Red Dog unit in Atlanta was known for terrorizing people and it was disbanded.
She went to Memphis.
She started the Scorpion unit, which actually involves the officers that murdered Tyree Nichols.
Complaints were made about this unit.
They fell on deaf ears and now, because of Tyree Nichols' death, they are disbanded.
Does that mean she deserves praise?
No.
Does that mean she is operating differently than the policing that has been taking place that we have been complaining about?
I'll get to the reason why this matters.
I see this quote from James Baldwin going around relating to the fact that the black men who were involved in this crime were just so relentless and people are shocked that a black man would do that to another black person.
I genuinely feel like y'all are not understanding that for many black people who enter the force, their race is now superseded by their involvement in this gang of thugs called police.
So, again, I will remind you, the culture of policing is greater than the individual.
Miss me with she's a black woman or they were black men.
These are cops.
And cops operate a certain way under the code of their culture.
What I mean is that, in my opinion, as a black person, once you become a police officer, you are no longer protected by the community of us.
That is forsaken and firstly choosing instead to protect the culture of them.
They're cops.